watemi.com 2014-02-28

# Privacy Policy | Watemi

**Privacy Policy for watemi.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [contact@watemi.com](mailto:contact@watemi.com).

At watemi.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by watemi.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, watemi.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
watemi.com use cookies.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser  
(if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

As you visit and browse our Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you  
from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Webserver’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate  
number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site  
and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you andwe do not intentionally store any personal  
information thatyour browser provided to us in your cookies.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on watemi.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to watemi.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on watemi.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

watemi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. watemi.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
;  
To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business,  
or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site  
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy  
Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may  
make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all  
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our  
[privacy policy](http://watemi.com/privacy-policy).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 06/15/2013

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the  
information below.
